[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Movie Gone with the Wind was the first feature length film shot entirely in color.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first Hollywood movie in which Alan Rickman appeared was Die Hard.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sportsman Jerry DePoyster is a record breaker in this category.", "correct_answer": "Shortest punt in the NFL", "incorrect_answers": ["Fastest 100 yard dash on roller skates", "Longest field goal in an NBA game", "Worst pass completion record in an NFL season"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If attacked by a shark it is recommended that you punch the shark in the nose.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tom Hanks co-starred in the TV program Bosom Buddies with this fine actor/juggler.", "correct_answer": "Peter Scolari", "incorrect_answers": ["Christopher Knight", "Steve Zahn", "Tom Everett Scott"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Alan Rickmans birth date?", "correct_answer": "February 21, 1946", "incorrect_answers": ["February 22, 1946", "January 21, 1946", "February 21, 1945"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The consumption of what type of insects is allowed by Jewish dietary laws?", "correct_answer": "Locust", "incorrect_answers": ["Beetle", "Cricket", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the only two landlocked countries in South America ?", "correct_answer": "Bolivia and Paraguay", "incorrect_answers": ["Paraguay and Uruguay", "Bolivia and Uruguay", "Colombia and  Ecuador"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Japanese car make was established in 1970, but the first automobile of the brand was released in 1917.", "correct_answer": "Mitsubishi", "incorrect_answers": ["Mazda", "Nissan", "Suzuki"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the King Penguin?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They are serially monogamous.", "Both parents take part in the incubation.", "The female lays 1 single egg."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the comedy film Superbad, Evan is going to attend Yale after he graduates from high school.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest one-day decline in recorded stock market history is called Black Monday and occurred on this date.", "correct_answer": "October 19, 1987", "incorrect_answers": ["September 22, 1964", "December 8, 1990", "November 23, 1982"]}]